Arabia
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Arabia
2.1.2.1.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1331
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Arabian “Hindu” bathing on deck of S.S. Ozarda, 1918; 1; 1-2; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Half of the nationalities represented on the S.S. Ozarda, 1918; 2; 1-3; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Sheep on board deck of S.S. Ozarda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Our fellow passengers crossing the Red Sea], 1918; 3; 1-5; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Sheep on board deck of S.S. Ozarda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Our fellow passengers crossing the Red Sea], 1918; 4; 1-5; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Sudanese sailor and sheep, 1918; 5; 1-7; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Sudanese sailor and sheep, 1918; 6; 1-7; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Sudanese sailor and sheep, 1918; 7; 1-7; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Scotch Highlander cooking on deck of S.S. Ozarda, 1918; 8; 1-8; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Scottish soldier and African on board deck of S.S. Ozarda, 1918; 9; 1-9; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Wadi Araba, caravan in distance, 1918; 10; 1-14; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Caravan in Wadi Araba, Lowell Thomas on camel in foreground with back to camera, 1918; 11; 1-16; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Camel caravan in Wadi Araba, Lowell Thomas on camel in foreground [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A camel caravan in the Wadi Arabia], 1918; 12; 1-17; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Wadi Ithm [?], 1918; 13; 1-18; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - British soldiers in automobile talking to Bedouins, 1918; 14; 1-20; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Camels and Arabs in Wadi Ithm [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Sidi” Lawrence and his “Sons”], 1918; 15; 1-21; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Arab prison camp, guard with rifle in foreground, 1918; 16; 1-24; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Bedouin department store, 1918; 17; 1-27; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Bedouin department store, 1918; 18; 1-27; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Bedouin Department store, 1918; 19; 1-29; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Jedda from sea, 1918; 20; 1-35; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Jedda from sea, 1918; 21; 1-35; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Masts of ships at Jedda, 1918; 22; 1-36; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Eve’s Tomb, Jedda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The last resting-place of the Mother of us all], 1918; 23; 1-40; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - Large hotel, Jedda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The Waldorf-Astoria of Arabia-including 200 rooms with accommodations for 1000 guests with all the latest Arabian conveniences excepting bath, ‘phone, light, heat, or service], 1918; 24; 1-41; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Large hotel, Jedda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The Waldorf-Astoria of Arabia-including 200 rooms with accommodations for 1000 guests with all the latest Arabian conveniences excepting bath, ‘phone, light, heat, or service], 1918; 25; 1-41; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - Large hotel, Jedda [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The Waldorf-Astoria of Arabia-including 200 rooms with accommodations for 1000 guests with all the latest Arabian conveniences excepting bath, ‘phone, light, heat, or service], 1918; 26; 1-41; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence standing, three quarter length [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The archeologist and poet who turned soldier], 1918; 27; 1-42; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence standing, three quarter length [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The archeologist and poet who turned soldier], 1918; 28; 1-42; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence standing, three quarter length [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The archeologist and poet who turned soldier], 1918; 29; 1-42; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence standing outdoors on a prayer rug [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Lawrence in front of his headquarters tent], 1918; 30; 1-44; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence, D. G. Hogarth, Allan Dawnay, full figure [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Colonel Lawrence conferring with Commander D. G. Hogarth, one of his advisers at the Arab Bureau in Cairo, 1918; 31; 1-45; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence in British uniform, grinning, three quarter figure [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Lawrence at headquarters in Cairo], 1918; 32; 1-45B; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence in British uniform, full figure, 1918; 33; 1-45C; 3x4 color (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence on camel, 1918; 34; 1-46; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence and his bodyguard in the desert [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Sidi” Lawrence and his “Sons”], 1918; 35; 1-47; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  - T. E. Lawrence and two Syrian advisors [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Lawrence confers with Arab Nationalists leaders from Bagdad and Damascus], 1918; 36; 1-48; 3x4 b&w (Box 1331)
  Box 1332
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - T. E. Lawrence and six of his British staff in front of tent [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: T. E. Lawrence in chair surrounded by members of his British staff], 1918; 1; 1-49; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence and six of his British staff in front of tent [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: T. E. Lawrence in chair surrounded by members of his British staff], 1918; 2; 1-49; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in white robe, ends of headdress back over shoulders, hands clasped, sword at waist, three quarter length [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: In his white robes Lawrence looked like a prophet], circa 1918 - 1921; 3; 1-50; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in white robe, ends of headdress back over shoulders, hands clasped, sword at waist, three quarter length [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: In his white robes Lawrence looked like a prophet], circa 1918 - 1921; 4; 1-50; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in white robe, ends of headdress back over shoulders, hands clasped, sword at waist, three quarter length [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: In his white robes Lawrence looked like a prophet], circa 1918 - 1921; 5; 1-50; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in paisley robe, squatting, full-faced, close-up [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Col. T. E. Lawrence], circa 1918 - 1921; 6; 1-52; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in paisley robe, squatting, full-faced, close-up [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Col. T. E. Lawrence], circa 1918 - 1921; 7; 1-52; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in paisley robe, squatting, full-faced, close-up [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Col. T. E. Lawrence], circa 1918 - 1921; 8; 1-52; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence sitting on floor, toe of boot showing, circa 1918 - 1921; 9; 1-53; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in white robe, three quarters front, hands behind back, headdress over shoulders, sword at waist, circa 1918 - 1921; 10; 1-55; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in white robe, three quarters front, hands behind back, headdress over shoulders, sword at waist, circa 1918 - 1921; 11; 1-55; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in paisley robe, three quarter view, both hands on sword, full-faced [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Colonel T. E. Lawrence, the mystery man of Arabia], circa 1918 - 1921; 12; 1-56; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence in white robe, three quarter view, full-faced, head cloth hanging down [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Shereef” Lawrence], circa 1918 - 1921; 13; 1-57; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence, full length, white robe, sword at waist, circa 1918 - 1921; 14; 1-62; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T. E. Lawrence, full length, white robe, sword at waist, circa 1918 - 1921; 15; 1-62; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T.E. Lawrence sitting on rug, hand on each knee, circa 1918 - 1921; 16; 1-63; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - T.E. Lawrence kneeling with folded arms, circa 1918 - 1921; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - T.E. Lawrence, profile, circa 1918 - 1921; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Colonel P. C. Joyce, second in command to T. E. Lawrence [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Colonel Joyce, Commander of the Arab “Regulars”], 1918; 19; 1-64; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Hussein Ibn Ali, King of the Hedjaz [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: King of the Hejaz, “Commander of the Faithful,” and founder of a new Arabian dynasty], 1918; 20; 1-65; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Hussein Ibn Ali, King of the Hedjaz [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: King of the Hejaz, “Commander of the Faithful,” and founder of a new Arabian dynasty], 1918; 21; 1-65; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Emir Feisal, now King of Mesopotamia (Irak)], 1918; 22; 1-66; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Emir Feisal, now King of Mesopotamia (Irak)], 1918; 23; 1-66; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - His Royal Highness Emir Feisal, 1918; 24; 1-67; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - His Royal Highness Emir Feisal, 1918; 25; 1-67; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - His Royal Highness Emir Feisal, 1918; 26; 1-67; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal, 1918; 27; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal, 1918; 28; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal, 1918; 29; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal, 1918; 30; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal in British army truck, Lowell Thomas stands at right, 1918; 31; 1-70; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal in British army truck, Lowell Thomas stands at right, 1918; 32; 1-70; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Auda Abu Tayi, center, and two brothers [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Sheik Auda Abu Tayi, the Bedouin Robin Hood], 1918; 33; 1-71; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  - Auda Abu Tayi, center, and two brothers [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Sheik Auda Abu Tayi, the Bedouin Robin Hood], 1918; 34; 1-71; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Mohammed Abu Tayi, 1918; 35; 1-72; 3x4 b&w (Box 1332)
  - Emir Feisal on horse, 1918; 36; 1-73; 3x4 color (Box 1332)
  Box 1333
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Emir Feisal on horse, 1918; 1; 1-73; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Mounted Bedouins [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Bedouin “Irregulars” ready for a raid on the Turks], 1918; 2; 1-74; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Mounted Bedouins [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Bedouin “Irregulars” ready for a raid on the Turks], 1918; 3; 1-74; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin with curls [see 1-80] [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A brigand from Jebel Druz], 1918; 4; 1-77; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin with curls [see 1-80] [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A brigand from Jebel Druz], 1918; 5; 1-77; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Arab man [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A Sheik of Araby], 1918; 6; 1-78; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab man [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A Sheik of Araby], 1918; 7; 1-78; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Arab man [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A Sheik of Araby], 1918; 8; 1-78; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin sheik on horse [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Tallal El-Hareidhin of Tafas], 1918; 9; 1-79; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin sheik on horse [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Tallal El-Hareidhin of Tafas], 1918; 10; 1-79; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin with curls holding rifle [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: An Arab Apollo], 1918; 11; 1-80; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin with curls holding rifle [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: An Arab Apollo], 1918; 12; 1-80; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Druses from Hauran [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Druses from the Hauran], 1918; 13; 1-81; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Druses from Hauran [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Druses from the Hauran], 1918; 14; 1-81; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Crowd of Bedouins squatting and standing, Solomon’s Mountains in background, 1918; 15; 1-82; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Bedouin barber shop at an oasis, 1918; 16; 1-83; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Scottish soldiers and Arabs at Akaba, 1918; 17; 1-84; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Head of Gulf of Akaba from shore, two ships in distance, 1918; 18; 1-85; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - British cruiser off Arabian coast, man in foreground, 1918; 19; 1-86; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Akaba waterfront [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Shore-line at the head of the Gulf of Akaba], 1918; 20; 1-87; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Akaba waterfront [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Shore-line at the head of the Gulf of Akaba], 1918; 21; 1-87; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Squatting Bedouins, close-up, with camels at Akaba, 1918; 22; 1-90; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Mazuk, vain Bedouin on Emir Feisal’s staff, 1918; 23; 1-91; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Distant view of camp beneath cliff at Gueira, Arab men standing in left foreground, 1918; 24; 1-92; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Abyssinian followers of Emir Feisal, 1918; 25; 1-94; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab cavalry under Malud Bey [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Malud Bey and his Arab cavalry], 1918; 26; 1-97; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab cavalry under Malud Bey [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Malud Bey and his Arab cavalry], 1918; 27; 1-97; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab cavalry under Malud Bey [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Malud Bey and his Arab cavalry], 1918; 28; 1-97; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Dinner party, left to right: Nuri Pasha, Auda Abu Tayi, Emir Feisal, Lowell Thomas, 1918; 29; 1-98; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Dinner party, left to right: Nuri Pasha, Auda Abu Tayi, Emir Feisal, Lowell Thomas, 1918; 30; 1-98; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Dinner party, left to right: Nuri Pasha, Auda Abu Tayi, Emir Feisal, Lowell Thomas, 1918; 31; 1-98; 3x4 b&w (Box 1333)
  - Emir Feisal and Lowell Thomas using field glasses to watch a battle at Maan, 1918; 32; 1-100; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab regular army drawn up at foot of hill, 1918; 33; 1-101; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Three armored cars in silhouette at sunset [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Armored cars in holy Arabia], 1918; 34; 1-102; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab battery in action, sunset, fighting near Damascus [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Lawrence’s mountain guns in action], 1918; 35; 1-104; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  - Arab battery in action, sunset, fighting near Damascus [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Lawrence’s mountain guns in action], 1918; 36; 1-104; 3x4 color (Box 1333)
  Box 1334
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Arab battery, not firing, 1918; 1; 1-105; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Little Arab boy with rifle, 1918; 2; 1-108; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Little Arab boy with rifle, 1918; 3; 1-108; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Little Arab boy with rifle, 1918; 4; 1-108; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Bedouin boy on right, 1918; 5; 1-109; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Jaffar Pasha addressing officers, 1918; 6; 1-110; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Jaffar Pasha addressing officers, 1918; 7; 1-110; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Bedouin cavalry and British armored cars in desert, 1918; 8; 1-111; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - General Nuri Pasha with staff and flag, 1918; 9; 1-112; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - General Nuri Pasha and staff greeting Lowell Thomas, 1918; 10; 1-115; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Five Bedouin horsemen, 1918; 11; 1-117; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Mountains of Edom near Petra, Lowell Thomas’s caravan in foreground [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Our caravan approaching the “Lost City”], 1918; 12; 1-118; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Mountains of Edom near Petra, Lowell Thomas’s caravan in foreground [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Our caravan approaching the “Lost City”], 1918; 13; 1-118; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Mountains of Edom, sunset [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Sunset over the mountain of Edom], 1918; 14; 1-120; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Mountains of Edom, sunset, near view, 1918; 15; 1-121; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Valley twelve miles wide running toward Petra, 1918; 16; 1-122; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Lowell Thomas having tea at Wadi Musa, 1918; 17; 1-125; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Old Bedouin with pipe, 1918; 18; 1-127; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Old Bedouin with pipe, 1918; 19; 1-127; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Wadi Musa Bedouins, 1918; 20; 1-128; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Roman soldiers’ tomb [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “The tomb of the Roman soldiers”], 1918; 21; 1-129; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Roman soldiers’ tomb [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “The tomb of the Roman soldiers”], 1918; 22; 1-129; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Roman soldiers’ tomb [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “The tomb of the Roman soldiers”], 1918; 23; 1-129; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Arab sheik on horse in front of tent, Petra, 1918; 24; 1-134; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir) from gorge, Arab in foreground, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A rose-red temple carved like a cameo from the face of the mountain], 1918; 25; 1-138; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir) from gorge, Arab in foreground, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: A rose-red temple carved like a cameo from the face of the mountain], 1918; 26; 1-138; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir) from gorge, Petra, 1918; 27; 1-139; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir) from gorge, Petra, 1918; 28; 1-139; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), men at foot of columns, Petra, 1918; 29; 1-140; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), men at foot of columns, Petra, 1918; 30; 1-140; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), men at foot of columns, Petra, 1918; 31; 1-140; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), men at foot of columns, Petra, 1918; 32; 1-140; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - In gorge approaching Petra, man sitting in foreground, 1918; 33; 1-144; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - In gorge approaching Petra, man sitting in foreground, 1918; 34; 1-144; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), camels among columns, Petra, 1918; 35; 1-145; 3x4 color (Box 1334)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), camels among columns, Petra, 1918; 36; 1-145; 3x4 b&w (Box 1334)
  Box 1335
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Lowell Thomas on camel under column at the Temple of Isis, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: We rode into the Auditorium on our camels], 1918; 1; 1-146; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), bushes in foreground, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Pharaoh’s Temple” or the “Temple of Isis”], 1918; 2; 1-147; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), bushes in foreground, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Pharaoh’s Temple” or the “Temple of Isis”], 1918; 3; 1-147; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), bushes in foreground, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: “Pharaoh’s Temple” or the “Temple of Isis”], 1918; 4; 1-147; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 11; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 12; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Temple of Isis (The Deir), 1918; 13; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Tomb at Petra, 1918; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Tomb at Petra, 1918; 15; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 16; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 17; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 18; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 19; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 20; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 21; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 22; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 23; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 24; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 25; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 26; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 27; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 28; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 29; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 30; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 31; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 32; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 33; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 35; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  - Petra, 1918; 36; 3x4 b&w (Box 1335)
  Box 1336
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Petra, 1918; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Petra, 1918; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Lowell Thomas drinking in a gorge near Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The narrow defile that leads to the “Lost City”], 1918; 13; 1-148; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Lowell Thomas drinking in a gorge near Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The narrow defile that leads to the “Lost City”], 1918; 14; 1-148; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Man on camel in gorge near Petra, 1918; 15; 1-149; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Harry Chase in front of tent, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Chase reads the Koran while Mohammed in the background takes aim at a circling hawk], 1918; 16; 1-150; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Harry Chase in front of tent, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Chase reads the Koran while Mohammed in the background takes aim at a circling hawk], 1918; 17; 1-150; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Harry Chase in front of tent, Petra [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: Chase reads the Koran while Mohammed in the background takes aim at a circling hawk], 1918; 18; 1-150; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Lowell Thomas having dinner in front of tent, Petra, 1918; 19; 1-151; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Lowell Thomas having dinner in front of tent, Petra, 1918; 20; 1-151; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Unfinished temples, Petra, man in foreground, 1918; 21; 1-152; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Side view, temples in cliffs near camp, Petra, 1918; 22; 1-153; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Side view, temples in cliffs near camp, Petra, 1918; 23; 1-153; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Amphitheatre [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: An amphitheatre hewn out of the mountain], 1918; 24; 1-154; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Amphitheatre [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: An amphitheatre hewn out of the mountain], 1918; 25; 1-154; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Small hill covered with temples, man in foreground, 1918; 26; 1-155; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Face in cliff, Petra, 1918; 27; 1-157; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Temple at end of bridge, distant, Petra, 1918; 28; 1-158; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Temple at end of bridge, distant, Petra, 1918; 29; 1-158; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Temple at end of bridge, close-up, Temple of Urn, Petra, 1918; 30; 1-159; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Governor’s tomb, soldier in foreground, Petra, 1918; 31; 1-160; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Governor’s tomb, soldier in foreground, Petra, 1918; 32; 1-160; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Poppy, close-up, 1918; 33; 1-161; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Bedouin and Poppy, 1918; 34; 1-163; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  - Three men lying among flowers, Petra, 1918; 35; 1-164; 3x4 color (Box 1336)
  - Three men lying among flowers, Petra, 1918; 36; 1-164; 3x4 b&w (Box 1336)
  Box 1337
- Arabia, 2.1.2.1.1
  - Australian soldier with rifle, 1918; 1; 1-166; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Bedouin bathing in altar, 1918; 2; 1-167; color (Box 1337)
  - Bedouin bathing in altar, 1918; 3; 1-167; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Lowell Thomas and Australian soldier at altar [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: We found altars and places of sacrifice on some of the mountains above Petra], 1918; 4; 1-168; color (Box 1337)
  - Lowell Thomas and Australian soldier at altar [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: We found altars and places of sacrifice on some of the mountains above Petra], 1918; 5; 1-168; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Phallic monolith, 1918; 6; 1-170; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Phallic monolith, Petra, 1918; 7; 1-171; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Lowell Thomas watches as Arabs play tag around phallic monolith, Petra, 1918; 8; 1-172; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Mount Hor, three men in foreground, Petra, 1918; 9; 1-173; color (Box 1337)
  - Tomb discovered by accident, Petra, 1918; 10; 1-181; b&w (Box 1337)
  - Rock waves [With Lawrence in Arabia caption: The rock seemed to swirl like watered silk], 1918; 11; 1-182; b&w (Box 1337)